Genie Chang

UI / UX Designer

+65 8118 7036 genie820126@gmail.com https://geniechang.com

Coming from a product design background to being an operation manager for 2 years in a foreign country, I have developed efficient problem-solving skills and communication skills. I solve problems from the root cause and see them from the bigger picture. I am also exposed to multiple cultures and various people from different backgrounds, which helped me in understand users' needs. I am driven to bring a silent experience to users because good design is invisible.

EXPERIENCE

Operation Manager

Zu How Industry (Thailand) Co., Ltd

Jun 2017 - Nov 2019, Thailand

- Coordinated between regional offices to ensure the delivery of company goals
- Ensured day to day operations proceeded in an orderly manner
- Led and delivered the company ERP integration project, in collaboration with external vendors

Design for Life Project 🥏

Feb 2016 - May 2016, Thailand

In partnership with **Habitat for Humanity**, this university project aimed to design a piece of furniture for people in need. With a team of three, a cooking station was developed and built for a family-run Som Tam stall.

- · Conducted on-site research and interview
- · Brainstormed ideas, designed and developed solutions, and built mockups with the team
- Iterated the design with continuous feedback from external stakeholders
- Built and delivered the final product

KNOWLEDGE TOOLS LANGUAGES

UI/UX design, wireframing, Figma, Sketch, InVision, Illustrator, English / Chinese

prototyping, design research, Photoshop, Basic knowledge of

product design HTML & CSS

EDUCATION

Assumption University

Bachelor of Fine and Applied Arts, 200

Product Design

2013 - 2017, Thailand

Chancellor State College

2009 - 2011, Australia